Buying your first home can feel like a big step.
It often begins before you have even found the right property.
An adviser can help you understand what you may be able to borrow, based on your individual circumstances and lender criteria — and it helps to know that as you start looking.
MortgageEasy helps you get started.
You can start your journey in your own time or book a conversation when you are ready.
Our technology helps your adviser understand your situation earlier so they can focus on what matters most.
When choosing a mortgage, your adviser will help you explore options that may suit your circumstances.
They can also help you prepare for the next steps.
When the time is right, your adviser can provide an Agreement in Principle.
Although this is not a mortgage offer, it can help you move forward with more clarity when you are ready to make an offer.
From your initial application to completion, your adviser works with your conveyancer and estate agent.
And when you finally open the door to your new home, it is your moment.
Your journey.
Made clearer.
Understand what you may be able to borrow.
Explore mortgage options with an adviser.
Get your Agreement in Principle.
Make your offer when you are ready.
Move in — and talk about protecting what matters.